Hello and welcome to this tutorial.
In this video we'll show you how you can
upload and edit an invoice.
So let's begin.
In the Document Wizard
we navigate to the invoice portal.
Then we press on upload
and drag and drop our invoices csv.
And now your invoice line
item should appear here.
But as you can see, there
seems to be a mistake in one of them.
So let's click on edit
and see what's going on here.
Down below you can see that
there seems to be no matching order number
for this order.
So we check our order number
and we discovered
that there seems to be a typo.
So let's fix that.
And now
so you can see the error disappeared.
At this stage we could already press save.
Move back to our overview
and send off our data.
However, we can also choose to upload
our additional documents,
which I'll show you how to do now.
First of all I'm
going to add our invoice document.
So I just drag and drop
our invoice PDF over here
and it should be uploaded.
Afterwards
we can add our additional documents.
It is possible to attach a packing list
and preference certificate.
So let's start off our packing list.
We just
drag and drop it over here.
We select the document type.
And now we have to make sure
that we
add the right document number.
And our document date.
Now let's add our preference document.
Here we also have to pick a subtype.
Then we add our document number
and the correct date.
And let's not forget our document as well.
Now that we are done
with those steps, we just press save.
And now we're back in our overview.
As you can see, all of our invoice
line items are now valid.
And as you might also notice,
our invoice document has also been linked
to all of our invoice line items.
This happens
because the invoice number is matching.
Our additional
documents, our packing list
and our preference certificate
has only been linked
to the first two invoice line items.
This is because these documents
only get linked to the invoice line items
with the same invoice number
and the same order number
as the invoice line item
that we originally attached it to.
So if we want to
add these documents to an invoice
line item with a different order
number, then we would have to select
this third position here.
Click on edit again and repeat the same
steps again that we just went over.
Now if you want to manually add
another invoice line item,
you can do so by pressing on the add
button up here.
If you want to delete a single invoice
line item,
you can do so
by pressing the delete button.
If you want to delete all the invoice
line items and the attached documents,
you can do so
by pressing on the Delete file button.
Then everything will be gone.
However,
since we're done with this exercise
and everything seems to be in order,
we'll just press send now.
And in a minute,
all of our documents would be gone.
In the next video, titled ‘Displaying
Sent Data’, we will show you how you can
look for the documents and invoices
that you have already sent.
Thank you for your attention.
I hope you're familiar now
with the process
of how to upload and edit an invoice.
If you have any more questions,
feel free to check in the user
manual
or do not be afraid to reach out to us.
Thank you. Bye bye.